http://www.acumentrics.com/privacy-policy

Welcome to Acumentrics, Inc.  website
This Privacy Policy applies to your use of this website. We created the policy to demonstrate our commitment to privacy and to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices. By visiting this site, you accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not accept these terms, please discontinue use of this website. Acumentrics may revise or amend this Privacy Policy at any time without notification, and the date of the current version is below.
Collection and Use of Personal InformationInformation may be automatically collected by our website, including your IP address, the address of the site you visited just prior to ours, and number of times an article or page from our site has been shared. Information may also be voluntarily provided by you, such as your name, address, telephone number, and/or email address.
Any non-public personal information (such as your name, address, phone number and email address) that you provide will be used for the purpose stated on the form or page where it is collected. Any non-public personal information that you provide may also be used to send you marketing and promotional communications; however, you may opt out at any time as instructed in such communications. We will not otherwise willfully disclose individually identifiable information about you to anyone outside Acumentrics without first receiving your permission, except to our affiliates, agents or service providers for the stated purpose. The recipient of your information will be obligated to protect it and use it only for the purpose for which it was provided, consistent with applicable laws and regulations. We also reserve the right to retain or disclose personal information when we believe that such action is necessary to respond to a legal or governmental inquiry, regulation or proceeding. If Acumentrics goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred.
Occasionally we may request additional or clarifying information from you in order to deliver any requested materials to you, respond to your questions, or deliver a quote, product or service.
If your personally identifiable information changes, you may update it by contacting us by email or postal mail at the contact information listed below.
E-Mail
We welcome your comments, questions, and suggestions, and throughout our site have email links and forms for your use. Your comments, questions, and requests will be addressed within a reasonable timeframe, by those Acumentrics employees assigned to addressing your specific concerns.
Please be aware that your e-mail, like most non-encrypted e-mail messages, while in transit to us, may be accessed by other Internet users without your knowledge and permission. Please do not use e-mail to communicate information to us that you consider confidential.
Cookies & Tracking Information
We use cookies on our website. A cookie is a piece of data that is stored on the hard drive of your computer and is used to identify your computer on return visits to our website. Cookies may be used to customize your visits and to monitor use of our website. If you block or decline to accept a cookie, you may still use our website; however, some parts of the website may not permit access and some functionality may be lost.
Note that when you visit our site, even if you just browse, read or download information, we do automatically collect information that does not identify you personally, but provides us with usage statistics (such as the number of unique visitors, pages visited most often, and how many visitors make use of our configuration tool) that help us to improve the overall experience of visitors in finding specific information and navigating through our site. This visitor tracking information includes the Internet Protocol (IP) address and domain name used, the type of browser and operating system you are using, the date and time of your visit, the web pages or services you accessed at this site and the referring web page.
Third Party Sites
Our website provides links to some other websites that are neither owned nor controlled by Acumentrics, but may be useful or of interest to you. Links to these non-Acumentrics sites do not constitute or imply an endorsement by Acumentrics. Acumentrics also is not responsible for the privacy practices embraced by other website owners, the accuracy, or content on the sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of any linked sites.
Security
Acumentrics has implemented security processes designed to protect non-public personal information, and we strive to follow generally accepted industry norms.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact:
Acumentrics, Inc.
Attn: Marketing Department
10 Walpole Park South
Walpole, MA 02081marketing@acumentrics.com
About us
About Acumentrics
News & Events
Management Team
Board of Directors
White paper
Rugged Blade UPS Parallel, Fault Tolerant and N+1 Operations
Download
White paper
Lithium ion Battery Packs Air Transportation: regulation, rules and practical guide
Download
White paper
Safety Comparison of different Lithium Ion Chemistries
Download
Get in touch
Contact us Live chat
Pack-Power™ System
Never Lose Power with Our Pack-Power™ System!
A Small Form Factor Advanced System with More Capability than a UPS, Power-Bank, and Battery Combined!
For any questionsView product
Pack-Power System
Tested to withstand
Cold temperature
Acumentrics Total Power Solutions including the RUPS™ are tested to the most stringent cold temperatures down to -20°C with LFP batteries. For solutions requiring lower temperatures, contact Acumentrics.
Learn more
Hot temperature
Acumentrics Total Power Solutions are field war zone proven and support very high temperatures with very long life and high reliability with LFP Chemistry up to 60°C. Storage at high temperatures is possible with a very limited effect on battery life.
Learn more
Blown Precipitation
Our unique heat exchanger Flo-thru™ technology, tunnel design and sealed enclosure provide maximum protection for internal components from damaging effects of blown precipitation and any other contaminants like dust, sand, moisture and others, delivering an unmatched reliability for our RUPS™ in combat zones harsh environment.
Learn more
Shock and vibration
All our RUPS™ used in communications and electronic power devices are tested and proven with extremely high reliability in combat zone extremely harsh environment for mobile applications with stringent shock and vibration abuse. They have been tested and passed MIL-STD-810G and MIL-S-901-D.
Learn more
Fault tolerant
Our Rugged Blade UPS™ is designed to support, resilient, fault tolerant, power systems, using an N+1 configuration, when clean power is mission critical. Acumentrics peer to peer relationship between the units with a "moving master, sliding slave" scheme delivers the highest possible reliability with up to 8 units in parallel using a very resilient N+1 Rugged Sync Bus™
white paper
Total Power Solutions
RUPS™
Acumentrics RUPS 1,000W to 2,400W series RUPS have achieved MIL-STD-810-G (environmental), MIL-STD-461-F (electro-magnetic interference), and MIL-STD-1275-D (steady state and transient voltages) certifications.
View products
PDB and PDU
The Rugged PDU and Rugged Backplane from Acumentrics eases power distribution, simplifies cabling and offers circular mil-spec connectors sealed with positive latching to protect against rain, wind, dust, blowing sand, humidity, vibration and shock.
View products
Battery Packs, Internal and External modules
LFP and Lead Acid battery packs provide low maintenance, high run time and enhanced cycle life. Acumentrics External Battery Modules (EBM) increase battery runtime.
View products
Cables & Racks accessories / Cabinets and Transit cases
Sampling of Acumentrics Rugged UPS accessories. Contact customer services at cs@acumentrics.com or at 844-787-7872 (844-RUPS-USA) to discuss your configuration needs.
View products
Acumentrics' Products
View
Why Acumentrics
Since 1994, Acumentrics engineering and manufacturing teams continue to deliver total power solutions that provide data center quality power to mission critical applications. Made in Walpole, MA (USA) Acumentrics total power solutions includes Rugged-UPS™ (Uninterruptible Power Supply), power conditioners, inverters, portable power and power distribution units that can be mounted in 19" racks, transit cases, roller cases, back packs and hand carried.
Read
Let's work together
Contact Acumentrics
Makers of Rugged-UPS™
Acumentrics is a leader in Rugged-UPS™ (AC and DC uninterruptible power supplies) for military and industrial power conditioning, backup power supplies, and other mission-critical applications.
Acumentrics, Inc.
10 Walpole Park
South Walpole, MA 02081
Toll-free Phone: 844-787-7872Toll-free Phone: 844-RUPS-USAPhone: 617-932-7877
First name
Last name
Company
Title
Email
Phone number
Service
Choose a serviceSales & ProductsCustomer serviceHuman ResourcesPublic RelationsWarranty & Repair service
What is your budget?
What type of UPS do you need?
Rugged
Industrial
Not sure
What is the best way to contact you?
Telephone
Email
What is the size of the load in watts?
Do you need DC input?
Yes
No
Not sure
Do you need DC output?
Yes
No
Not sure
If you need DC output, please choose from the following load requirements
150W
250W
600W
1000W
2000W
Note: These are available on the ACG2500 Series only. DC output for the ACG1252 Series is 150W.
If you need DC output, please choose from the following voltage
12V
24V
28V
48V
Which AC output do you need?
120V/60Hz
220V/60Hz (available on ACG2500 Series only)
230V/60Hz (available on ACG2500 Series only)
Not sure
None
Do you need battery backup?
Yes
No, conditioning only
Not sure
What is the desired runtime at full-load?
If you would like a quote prepared for you, please choose the quantity
1-25
26-100
101-250
251+
End User Application Type
Military
Commercial
Government
Region
United States
Other
State
StateAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaGuamHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming
Country
To apply to an Acumentrics position, please use the application form.
For Warranty & Repair service, please contact Acumentrics at repairs@acumentrics.com.
Comments
Call back & Acumentrics news
Please have someone call me about Acumentrics' products.
Yes, I would like to receive Acumentrics' news.
Send
Acumentrics, Inc.
10 Walpole Park South
Walpole, MA 02081
